<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CSI Delhi-NCR Chapter</string>
    <string name="Open_drawer">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="Close_drawer">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about_csi">Computer Society of India is a body of computer professionals in India. It was started
on 6 March 1965 by a few computer professionals and has now grown to be the national
body representing computer professionals. It has 72 chapters across India, 511 student
branches, and 100,000 members.
The Computer Society of India is a non-profit professional meet to exchange views
and information to learn and share ideas. The Society also encourages and assists
professionals to maintain integrity and competence of the profession and fosters a sense
of partnership amongst members. Besides the activities held at the Chapters and
Student Branches, the Society also conducts periodic conferences and seminars. The
Society functions under the guidance of an Executive Committee. The Functional head
of the Society is the President and is assisted by the Vice President, Executive, Co-executive and other teams.
CSI aims to advance and promote the science and practice of computing and IT in
India, as well as to facilitate communication and collaboration among its members. It
provides a platform for professionals, researchers, educators, and students to share their
knowledge, experiences, and ideas through conferences, seminars, and workshops.</string>

    <string name="about_srm">SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Ghaziabad was established in the year 1997
and houses over 5,000 students, over 200 faculties, and a plethora of visiting faculty
from across industries. It is a private university located in Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh,
India. The university offers undergraduate, postgraduate, and doctoral programs in
various fields such as engineering, management, computer applications, pharmacy and
sciences.
The Ghaziabad campus of SRM Institute of Science and Technology is spread over an
area of 25 acres and is equipped with modern infrastructure, including state-of-the-art
laboratories, libraries, and classrooms. The campus has a vibrant student community,
with students from all over the country and the world. SRM Institute of Science and
Technology, Ghaziabad campus also has collaborations with several international
universities, which allows students to gain a global perspective on their education. The
university also provides various facilities to its students, including sports facilities,
accommodation, and medical facilities.
Overall, SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Ghaziabad campus is a reputed
institution known for its quality education and excellent infrastructure.
</string>

    <string name="about_cse_department">The CSE Department of SRMIST, NCR provides an outstanding research environment
complemented by excellence in teaching. They provide a lot of opportunities for their
students, like they organize many workshops, webinars etc. The training imparted aims
to prepare young minds for the challenging opportunities in the IT industry. The
teachers in SRM provide practical knowledge that makes the students suitable for IT
sector jobs. The CSE department in SRM also manages to welcome many big
companies for the students so that they get placed in a good company and their future
is secured.</string>
</resources>